// const dayFiveQuestions = [
//   {
//     question: "Who is obligated to pay Zakath?",
//     options: [
//       "Muslims who possess wealth more than the Nisab level for a period of one full lunar year",
//       "Zakath is obligatory for all Muslims",
//       "Zakath is only obligatory for business establishments",
//       "Zakath is not obligatory at all",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "What is the percentage of Zakat which Muslims pay?",
//     options: ["1.5%", "2.5%", "3.5%", "4.5%"],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Can Zakath be given to those who are in debt?",
//     options: [
//       "No, it is not permissible to give Zakath to people who are in debt",
//       "Yes, Zakath can be given to those who are in debt",
//       "Zakath should not be given to any person",
//       "None of the above",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "How does Zakath encourage socio-political responsibility among Muslims?",
//     options: [
//       "Zakath encourages Muslims to organise social get-togethers and parties",
//       "Zakath encourages Muslims to spend money in travelling to new places",
//       "Zakath encourages Muslims to redistribute wealth and boosts social responsibility",
//       "Zakath encourages Muslims to build new houses for themselves",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 2,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "How frequently do Muslims have to pay Zakath?",
//     options: ["Yearly", "Half Yearly", "Quarterly", "Monthly"],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "What is the meaning of Zakath?",
//     options: ["To spend", "To receive", "Purification", "None of the above"],
//     correctOption: 2,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "How many categories of people are eligible to receive Zakath?",
//     options: [
//       "Five Categories",
//       "Six Categories",
//       "Seven Categories",
//       "Eight Categories",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "In which month did Zakat become obligatory?",
//     options: ["Muharram", "Rajab", "Sha'ban", "Ramadan"],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "What is the minimum threshold of wealth for Zakat to be obligatory?",
//     options: ["Nisab", "Fitr", "Sadqah", "Khums"],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "What is the term for the obligatory charity given before the Eid prayers?",
//     options: ["Sadaqah", "Amanah", "Zakat-ul-Fitr", "Lillah"],
//     correctOption: 2,
//   },
// ];

const dayFiveQuestions=[
  {
    question: "Which prophet did the shayaatheen (devils) attribute the teaching of magic and witchcraft to?",
    options: ["Adam AS", "Sulaiman AS", "Dawud AS", "Ibrahim AS"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "They followed the magic promoted by the devils during the reign of Solomon. Never did Solomon disbelieve, rather the devils disbelieved. (Surah Baqarah 101-102)"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following prophets came before Idrees AS?",
    options: ["Adam AS", "Nuh AS", "Hud AS", "Saalih AS"],
    correctOption: 0,
    justification: "Prophet Adam AS was the first prophet created by Allah. (Stories of the Prophets)"
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the grandfather of prophet Yusuf AS?",
    options: ["Ismaeel AS", "Is'haq AS", "Ibraheem AS", "Ya’qoob AS"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "The Prophet (ﷺ) said, 'The honourable, the son of the honourable, the son of the honourable, (was) Yusuf, the son of Ya'qoob, the son of Ishaq, the son of Ibraaheem.' (Sahih Al-Bukhari 3390)"
  },
  {
    question: "How were the people of 'Aadh destroyed?",
    options: ["By floods", "By an earthquake", "By a strong wind", "By a fire"],
    correctOption: 2,
    justification: "They were destroyed by a furious, bitter wind. (Surah Al-Haqqah 6-7)"
  },
  {
    question: "Which Prophet was sent to the people of 'Aad?",
    options: ["Shuaib AS", "Hud AS", "Ilyaas AS", "Idrees AS"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "And to the people of ’Âd We sent their brother Hûd. (Surah A'raaf 65)"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the prophet sent to the people of Thamud?",
    options: ["Hud AS", "Saalih AS", "Alyasa AS", "Yahya AS"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "The people of Thamûd rejected the messengers. (Surah Ash-Shura 141-142)"
  },
  {
    question: "What was the miracle given to the prophet Saalih AS?",
    options: ["A she-camel that came out of stone", "Splitting of the moon", "Walking on water", "Flying"],
    correctOption: 0,
    justification: "This is Allah’s she-camel as a sign to you. (Surah A'raaf 73)"
  },
  {
    question: "In Surah Baqarah, two names Haaroot and Maaroot are mentioned. What does these names refer to?",
    options: ["Two men", "Two shayatheen or devils", "Two towns", "Two Angels"],
    correctOption: 3,
    justification: "They taught magic to the people. (Surah Baqarah 102)"
  },
  {
    question: "What was the first mosque that was built on earth?",
    options: ["Masjid al Haram", "Masjid al Aqsa", "Masjid al Nabawi", "Masjid Quba"],
    correctOption: 0,
    justification: "The first mosque built was Al-Masjid-ul-Haram. (Bukhari 3425)"
  },
  {
    question: "Which prophet is mentioned most in the Qur'an?",
    options: ["Muhammad (ﷺ)", "Isah AS", "Musa AS", "Adam AS"],
    correctOption: 2,
    justification: "Musa AS is mentioned 136 times in the Qur'an, more than any other prophet."
  }
];
 export default dayFiveQuestions;
